techably.com 2014-11-30

# Privacy Policy

At [TechAbly.com](http://techably.com/ "TechAbly.com"), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the type of personal information which is received and collected by the website and how it is used.

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of TechAbly.

We have a strict no spam policy and do not send you any emails, unless you subscribe to receive email updates.

### About Credit Cards

TechAbly will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you DO NOT enter it on any of the forms on TechAbly.

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, TechAbly also makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes Internet Protocol (IP) Addresses, Type of Browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), Date / Time stamp, Referring / Exit Pages, and Number of clicks to analyze Trends, Administer the Site, Track user’s movement around the site, and gather Demographic Information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

A “ _cookie_ ” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows TechAbly to recognize you each time you visit this site(customization etc.). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and TechAbly does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as news feeds.

TechAbly does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

#### DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – [www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/)

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> to Opt-out.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Our privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

### Visitor Tracking / Statistical Analysis

TechAbly makes use of analytical software such as _Google Analytics_ for statistical purposes. For the stat analysis purpose, your IP (Internet Protocol) address, browser, screen resolution, operating system are captured. We, at TechAbly, use this information only for statistical purpose and do not share it with any third party.

### User Comments

TechAbly allows users to comment on the site. However, we hold all rights to accept or reject any comments based on our discretion. While commenting on TechAbly, please refrain from using content that is not suitable.

### Email Address

When you make a comment or contact us using the [Contact Page](http://techably.com/contact), your E-mail Address is required. Please be assured that your E-mail address will only be used for responding to your E-mail or Comment and will never be made publicly available. We will never sell your email address to any third parties, ever.

Feel free to contact the blog Author using the [contact page](http://techably.com/contact) for any other query / information.
